I woke up this morning and I was immediately angered because I just, I thought about how
wildly opportunistic someone has to be, how wildly privileged and self-centered someone has to be
to have not only the access to information, but the capabilities to access information and choose
not to, in order to prevent themselves from having to feel the truth, because then you have to fight it,
say it. You have to fight for the truth. You have to actually say for the truth, say the truth.
And I, I, I'm, I'm, I'm so bothered because that's what so many of you all are doing.
Like so many of y'all just don't want to know the truth because it undermines the lie you've been
telling yourself. It undermines the lie you've been telling yourself. And now for the first time,
I'm seeing actually a groundswell of folks who are like, you know what? Fuck it. Fuck it. We're just
going to say what it is. We have to, because look at what they're doing to these people. Look at how
they are eradicating these people and try to you. And you're allowing it for, for what? For what?
I see people trying to tell me I'm anti-Semitic. Get the fuck out of here. Incorrect. People trying
to say, oh, you know, it's, it's really, we have to protect all lives. Obviously. Yes. However,
you cannot consistently talk about all lives, all lives, all lives. If you were never talking about
the consistency of harming an entire group of people and how that actually is what put the Jewish
people in Israelis, in Israel's lives in danger. You cannot. And stop fucking trying to convince
me of otherwise. And stop trying to convince yourself of otherwise. It is completely disingenuous.
It's mealy mouthed and is unintellectual and it is not compassionate. It is not reflection of faith.
It is not a reflection of humanity. It is a reflection of ignorance and colonial settler
opportunism. Cut it the fuck out. And anybody saying that they don't know how to feel about
this issue is a fucking full of shit person. They are a full of shit person if they don't know
how to feel about what is happening. It's happening. Like in front of your face. It's happening.
In front of your face. And you don't know how to feel about that. Maybe it's because you don't want
to look. And that is what needs to really be addressed.